<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Library</string>
    <string name="book_info">More Info</string>
    <string name="home_name">Library</string>
    <string name="Preference_file_name">Home</string>
    <string name="todo">TODO</string>
    <string name="book1_name">Dark-Things</string>
    <string name="author1_name">Author :- SUKANYA VENKATRAGHAVAN</string>
    <string name="book1_about">\t\t\tCombining fantasy with the rich tapestry of folklore,Dark Things is a strange fairytale wrought of intrigue and enchantment,of shadows and secrets, of evil and those who battle it.</string>
    <string name="book2_name">GameWorld-Trilogy</string>
    <string name="author_2">Author :- SAMIT BASU</string>
    <string name="book2_about">\t\t\tThree books, The Simoqin Prophecies, The Manticore’s Secret and The Unwaba Revelations, form the three parts of The GameWorld Trilogy.
\t\t\tThe trilogy narrates the reawakening of the terrible rakshas, Danh-Gem, and the arrival of a hero to face him.</string>
    <string name="book3_name">MURDER IN A MINUTE</string>
    <string name="author3_name">Author :- SHOUVIK BHATTACHARYA</string>
    <string name="book3_about">\t\t\tIn Murder in a Minute, when a young woman is found lifeless in a pool of her own blood, everyone is convinced that it is her college sweetheart who murdered her.
\t\t\tThe victims step-brothers, Rishabh and Arya arent so convinced. They embark on a journey to unearth the truth, a journey riddled with fallacies and conspiracies, planted intentionally to trap them.</string>
    <string name="book4_name">PATANG</string>
    <string name="author4_name">Author :- BHASKAR CHATTOPADHYAY</string>
    <string name="book4_about">\t\t\tIn Patang, a man is found brutally murdered, his body posed like a kite on the tallest cell tower in the city.

\t\t\tAs one corpse after another turns up in the unlikeliest of places, maverick investigator Chandrakant Rathod has to pit his sharp instincts against the machinations of the sadistic, ruthless killer.
</string>
    <string name="book5_name">SACRED GAMES </string>
    <string name="author5_name">Author :- VIKRAM CHANDRA</string>
    <string name="book5_about">\t\t\t\t\t\tSacred Games draws the reader deep into the life of Inspector Sartaj Singh, and into the criminal underworld of Ganesh Gaitonde, the most wanted gangster in India.

\t\t\tIt it is a story of friendship and betrayal, of terrible violence, of an astonishing modern city and its dark side.</string>
    <string name="book6_name">SPY IN THE AMBER</string>
    <string name="author6_name">Author :- MANOHAR MALGONKAR</string>
    <string name="book6_about">\t\t\tSpy in the amber first published in 1971, is set during the time when tensions between India and China were at its peak.

\t\t\tHidden away from the world, in the deep belly of the Himalayas lies the Ragyabas monastery which has a treasure worth millions in its possession.

\t\t\tFearing Chinese invasion, the head monk decides to hand over the treasure to India for safe-keeping. But, the Chinese have different plans.</string>
    <string name="book8_name">THE MURDER OF SONIA RAIKKONEN</string>
    <string name="author8_name">Author :- SALIL DESAI</string>
    <string name="book8_about">\t\t\tIn The Murder of Sonia Raikkonen, late one November night, the mutilated corpse of a young Finnish tourist is found in a public garden in Pune.

\t\t\tIt looks like a case of brutal rape and murder, but Senior Inspector Saralkar and PSI Motkar find themselves probing further….delving deeper.</string>
    <string name="book7_name">THE DEVOURERS</string>
    <string name="author7_name">Author :- INDRA DAS</string>
    <string name="book7_about">\t\t\tThe Devourers is set during the reign of the Mughal Empire in the seventeenth century and extends to modern India.

\t\t\tIt features Shape-shifters, more specifically werewolves, and explores the concepts of love, cannibalism, and what it means to be human.

\t\t\tIt is told in a multi-layered manner, alternating between different time periods and perspectives.</string>
    <string name="SignUp_txt">Dont have account? <u>Sign up</u></string>
    <string name="login_txt">Already have account? <u>Login</u></string>
    <string name="menu_1">Dashbord</string>
    <string name="menu_4">Log out</string>
    <string name="menu_3">About App</string>
    <string name="menu_2">profile</string>
    <string name="open_drawer">Open Drawer</string>
    <string name="close_drawer">Close Drawer</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="Dashbord_fragment">Dashbord fragment</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="profile_fragment">profile fragment</string>
    <string name="about_fragment">about App fragment</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="logout_fragment">logout fragment</string>
</resources>